{
    "subject": "resource/Andrea_Ferro",
    "predicate": "property/dateOfBirth",
    "object": "1973-08-19",
    "human_readable": "Andrea Ferro was born on August 19, 1973.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8938580751419067,
            "question": "August 19th of what year marks Andrea Ferro's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8687232732772827,
            "question": "When was Andrea Ferro born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7985258102416992,
            "question": "How old was Andrea Ferro on August 19th, 2023?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7340593934059143,
            "question": "What is Andrea Ferro's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6531199216842651,
            "question": "Did Andrea Ferro have a birthday recently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6413841247558594,
            "question": "What month and day was Andrea Ferro born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5799685120582581,
            "question": "What is Andrea Ferro's age?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4724150002002716,
            "question": "In what year did Andrea Ferro come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3714566230773926,
            "question": "Is Andrea Ferro older than 50?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28101232647895813,
            "question": "If today is October 26th, 2023, how many days have passed since Andrea Ferro's birthday?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Andrea Ferro was born on August 19, 1973.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1362_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Andrea Ferro older than 50?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1362_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Andrea Ferro come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1362_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Andrea Ferro's age?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1362_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1362_80.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Andrea Ferro's birthdate, which matches the triple statement. The document with file_path \"/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_1362/re-ranker-msmarco/40.txt\" mentions that Andrea Ferro was born in Gallarate on May 1992, but this is likely an error or a different person altogether. However, the other documents confirm that Andrea Ferro's birthdate is August 19, 1973, as stated in the triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide the birth date of Andrea Ferro as \"19 August, 1973,\" which matches the query stating that he was born on \"August 19, 1973.\" Therefore, the information supports the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}